

ABOUT ME

I'm Maria, 26 years old and passionate about front-end development, design, animation, video, and every related field of multimedia.

I can describe myself as a graphic designer, web developer and multimedia specialist with knowledge acquired through academic degrees, e-learning and professional training.

SKILLS

- Graphic Design
- UI/UX Design
- Web Development
- Graphic Animation
- Video Editing
- 3D Animation
- 3D Modelling
- Virtual Reality
- Augmented Reality
- Social Media Design
- Videogame Development
- Audio Editing

CONTACTS





inkedin.com/in/maria-terroso/

MARIA TERROSO

EXPERIENCE

Jul 2023 - Aug 2023

Web Designer • Wiremaze

Web designer using technologies such as Adobe XD, Photoshop, Illustrator, JavaScript, SCSS/SASS and HTML.

Jan 2023 - Aug 2023

Fullstack Web Developer • RC Dental Clinics

Solo development of the website: https://rcdentalclinics.pt

July 2019 - Aug 2023

Social Media Designer • RC Dental Clinics

Creation of visually appealing and engaging content for RC Dental Clinics. This content helps the brand effectively communicate its message on various social media platforms.

April 2017 - June 2019

Graphic Content and Logo Designer ● RC Dental Clinics

Creation of visually appealing and engaging content for RC Dental Clinics. This content helps the brand effectively communicate its message on various social media platforms.

EDUCATION

Polytechnic Institute of Porto - Higher School of Media Arts and Design

- Degree in Multimedia, 09/2020-07/2023
- Level in EQF Level 6 | Final Grade 16

IEFP of Viana do Castelo

- Technician in Multimedia, 03/2017-07/2019
- Level in EQF Level 4 | Final Grade 18

SKILLS (EXTENDED)

- Web Development: Angular | JavaScript | TypeScript | SASS(SCSS) |
 Bootstrap | HTML | SQL | Git | Node.js | PHP | Node.js | MySQL
- **Design:** Adobe Photoshop | Adobe Illustrator | Icon Design | Canva | Social Media Management Social Media Ads
- UI/UX Design: Adobe XD | Figma | General UI/UX Design
- 2D/3D Animation and 3D Modelling: Autodesk MotionBuilder |
 Autodesk Mudbox | Autodesk 3ds Max | Autodesk Maya | Animation
 Design | 3D Modelling | Adobe Animate
- Interactive Media: Processing Programming Language | TouchDesigner | Cycling '74 Max/MSP/Jitter